There she is!
Bea Bishop, my girl!
Ready to dive back into
the grit of live theatre?
Hi, Mom.
Everybody is so excited
to see you direct
The Taming of the Shrew.
Where is your TV star?
Her name is Hannah,
not "TV Star."
I know that.
Award-winning actress
Hannah Michaels!
The coup of this summer's
Shakespeare Festival,
thanks to you!
Publicity's ramping up
promotion.
Well, when she said
that she wanted to do a play
during her break, I knew
it was a great opportunity
for both of us.
By the way, thank you so much
for scheduling our play
last in the season
so that she would have
an opportunity
to finish shooting her series.
Well, the main show
in the outdoor theatre
is always the last one up,
so it worked out.
You got four weeks rehearsals,
and then your play opens.
I'm ready.
- You're finally home.
- I'm thrilled.
I love that with live theatre
anything can happen.
Well, theatre is in your blood.
I'll never forget little you
running around backstage
asking all the stagehands
to let you open the curtain.
Oh, I was so precocious.
Everybody loved
having you around.
Especially after your dad left.
It was just you and me
against the world.
Yeah, what a time.
And now you're back.
And you have
charted your own path.
Yeah, out of your shadow, Mom.
I couldn't be prouder.
So, Hannah is, uh,
meeting the rest of the cast
at the tavern?
Yes.
Yeah, I thought it would be
a good, cozy place
to introduce her
to her castmates.
By the way, I didn't see
anybody listed
- for the role of Petruchio.
- Right, I'm...
It's a tough part to cast
because he's the male
romantic lead of the show,
so you need a strong actor
with presence, charisma.
But he's also the kind of guy
that you fall in love with,
even though he drives you nuts.
When's the next round
of auditions?
Actually,
I've already cast him, darling.
Oh!
So, who's playing Petruchio?
Hey, how are ya?
Oh, Benny, my dear.
Back from the national tour.
How did your Death of a Salesman
play before audiences?
Sellouts everywhere,
rave reviews.
As I would have expected.
But I'm almost relieved
to come home to Shakespeare
every season.
Hi, Benny.
Hey.
Bea?
Um, you're...
visiting your mom.
That's... that's nice.
How long you in town for?
Oh, no, I'm actually directing
Taming of the Shrew.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Well, that's news to me.
I'm playing Petruchio
in Taming of the Shrew.
That is news to me.
You both know I can't resist
a dramatic reveal.
- No, no...
- Yeah, no, it's fine.
Couldn't care less.
This season
has to end with a bang.
The final show is the one
that everybody waits for.
We've already got a buzz
going on about Hannah Michaels,
and we have record sign-ups
for this year's Young Friends
of the Fest events.
And Benny, would you reconsider
teaching at
the actors' workshop?
We've got a waiting list.
You know, you're kind of
a legend around here.
No.
Thank you.
Uh...
I don't wanna
spread myself too thin.
Right.
The play's the thing.
And you two,
back together again.
I have full faith that you're
going to be able to set your...
differing views aside.
It's been so long since
I was here directing a play.
Five years.
What's that, uh,
Winter's Tale quote,
"What's past is prologue"?
That's from The Tempest.
- Close enough.
- Mm, not really.
And it's settled, then.
Bea, I really have to have
a private word with you.
Mom, can it wait?
I have my...
We have our first
read-through of the play.
- Actually, it can't.
- Oh.
Yeah, sure, I'll be...
I'll be right there.
I'll see you at the tavern,
then, soon.
Wouldn't miss it.
I put in a special order
of Macbeth's Scotch Eggs.
Get everyone
in the Shakespeare mood.
I'm bringing pizza.
Perfect.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Oh, please.
I power-walked a 5K this morning
before you even
rolled out of bed.
Of course you did.
So, what's up?
I am...
retiring, Bea.
At the end
of this festival season.
Wow.
Mom, are you sure?
I mean, I knew
it was a possibility...
You know I've given my
whole life to this festival.
My heart, my soul...
It's your baby.
No, you're my baby.
- But the festival is...
- Your legacy.
Yeah, but you can't really
have a legacy unless you leave.
So, it's time.
Well, Mom, I have
a crazy idea to pitch you.
Oh, I bet.
Don't try to stop me.
Let me just say it out loud.
Okay, Bea.
I wanna take over the festival.
Yes.
Bea...
Before you argue,
let me tell you why.
Okay, wow.
Okay.
I have been working here
since I was born.
I know this place
inside and out.
I've learned
from the very best...
from you.
I have the grace and I have
the expertise that's necessary.
- Yes, Bea.
- I've been finding
new, exciting ways
to share Shakespeare
with a younger audience.
Yes, Bea, stop talking
long enough to hear me.
When somebody says yes,
you can stop pitching.
Wait, but, Mom, I thought
you would feel like it was...
No, Bea, you're right.
It is your destiny, sweetheart.
I was just worried that
maybe you wouldn't want it
because of your
TV directing career.
I want it.
I want it badly.
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes, yes, yes!
I have a meeting with
the board president Juan
next week.
You should be there.
Anything you need.
Let's go meet with Juan.
I'm so glad
to hear you say this.
I'm so happy for you.
Mom...
And I'm ready.
I have to go and introduce
Hannah to the cast
- at the tavern, so I'm gonna go.
- Off you go.
- The play's the thing.
- Play's the thing.
Hannah, hi!
- Bea!
- Hi!
Oh, thank you so much
for agreeing to do this.
Are you kidding? I've always
wanted to do theatre,
but I've never had the chance.
You're gonna be so great.
Well, this play is gonna
help people see me
- as a more serious actress.
- That's what you are.
So, how's
the memorization going?
It's a lot of lines.
Yeah, it's coming along.
Yeah, almost there.
Okay.
I cannot wait to meet
the rest of the cast.
They're so great.
They can't wait either.
- Ooh, fun! Can I have a beer?
- No, you cannot.
This is a professional
environment.
Well, you're the one who decided
to have a rehearsal in a pub.
Okay, the read-through
was supposed to begin
10 minutes ago.
Meet Doug Berrie.
This is our stage manager.
Pleased to meet you,
Ms. Michaels.
Oh, Doug, please call me Hannah.
- Mm-hm.
- Please.
Yeah, I will call you
whatever you want,
as long as you sign in
on time every day.
- He's funny.
- Yeah, I'm not joking.
Time's ticking.
Here we go.
Pitter-patter, come on.
Okay.
He cares a lot.
Now, listen,
you're the new guy here,
so it's okay if it takes you
a while to warm up to them.
Hi, everybody!
- I'd say she's all warmed up.
- Yeah, that was easy.
Um, Hannah, I'd like
to introduce you to Maggie.
She's playing your sister,
Bianca.
She's also your understudy
as Kate.
- Hi, Baya!
- Oh, it's actually "Bee-a."
Short for Beatrice.
Like...
"To Be-a or not to Be-a."
Right. So sorry.
It's only my second year.
It's totally fine.
Happens all the time.
This is Don.
He's playing one of the suitors.
And this is Clay.
He's gonna be playing
another one of your suitors.
Hi, there.
I'm Hannah.
I know.
Nice to meet you.
You know, Hortensio and Kate
don't have many scenes together.
- That's a shame.
- Alright, everybody.
I took the liberty
of ordering us
a couple of rounds
of Macbeth's Scotch Eggs.
Get us in the mood.
Joy?
I'd like to say a few words,
but we are actually waiting
for our leading man, Petruchio...
Hello!
Team Shakespeare Fest!
I've returned
from the touring war
that is the Death of a Salesman,
and I brought riches
from our plunder!
It's pizza, Benny.
Just say you brought pizza.
I brought pizza!
Last tour stop was New Haven,
and I got classic
Sal's Pizza for everyone!
Mmm, still warm!
We were just talking about this!
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho.
Benny, I was just about
to say a few words.
You can't say words
and enjoy a perfect slice
at the same time?
Well, I wouldn't wanna
talk with my mouth full.
Well, you're missing out.
You haven't changed a bit,
Gersten.
Why mess with perfection?
Whoever called you perfect
was lying to your pretty face.
Oh?
You think I have a pretty face?
Ah, except you got a little
pizza sauce right there.
We can hear you guys,
just so you know.
I think I actually
missed the low hum
of you two squabbling.
Just like old times.
Hannah,
I'd like to introduce you
to Benny Gersten.
He's playing your Petruchio.
I apologize in advance.
- Right. Hannah.
- Yeah.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry...
Can we have a quick sidebar?
Okay, uh, finish up your pizza
and then maybe let's team up
for a warm-up.
Maybe Roses, Buds, Thorns?
Wait, wait, roses and what?
I'll be back in a sec.
Okay, what is the deal
with those two?
I heard just after college,
they played Romeo and Juliet
and fell in love,
and then when the play ended,
so did their relationship.
Benny's a nomad actor,
but his love of
classical Shakespeare
always brings him back here.
Whenever Bea
directs at the festival,
this is the way it is with them.
Interesting.
I'm a little surprised that you
wanted to direct
Taming of the Shrew.
Given that it's about a daughter
being married off like property.
I don't treat Shakespeare
as sacrosanct like you do.
I'm gonna find a way
to make this play connect
with today's audience.
Historical context matters.
This festival is a love letter
to classic Shakespeare.
We respect it
by doing it classically.
Well, all the parts
were played by men back then.
Can't wait to see you
lace up in a corset
to play Lady Macbeth
the classical way.
Look, all I'm saying is nobody
wants to see modern dance
with some Elizabethan words
thrown in.
Or the story of Romeo,
the emo influencer,
and Juliet,
a true crime podcaster.
See, I actually think
that sounds amazing.
Of course it does.
To you.
You set A Midsummer Night's
Dream at a college rave.
You made
the entire audience dance,
and I don't dance.
Not even with a glow stick.
You saw that production?
And I... I have notes.
Which is exactly why I shouldn't
be playing Petruchio.
- Are you quitting on me?
- No, I'm not quitting.
I'm just not playing the lead
in a show that you're directing.
I'll, uh,
play some smaller role.
It'll have to be a role swap.
Any suggestions?
Clay.
I think he's paid his dues
playing supporting roles.
He's your best choice
to play opposite Hannah.
You seem awfully sure of this.
I know the company
better than you.
Hey!
It's not a criticism.
It's just a fact.
You've been away
a long time, Bea.
Quick update.
The role of Petruchio
will now be played by Clay.
Me...?
You'll be great, Clay.
You will.
I love it.
And that means, Benny,
I hereby grant you
the role of Hortensio.
Oh!
A role I could do blindfolded
with one hand
tied behind my back.
You know, I've always thought
Hortensio was actually a dancer.
Don't you dare.
Okay, everyone,
grab your scripts and a water.
We're gonna start
the table read.
No, Hannah and Clay
as the two leads is much better.
Thank you.
Did you just thank me?
What planet are you from,
and what have you done
with Bea Bishop?
Alright, tell me the truth.
Why did you really
not wanna play Petruchio?
I already told you.
- You wanna know what I think?
- Not really.
But I suspect
you're gonna tell me anyway.
I think you were afraid
Hannah Michaels
was gonna outshine you.
Not at all.
It doesn't hurt me
to see another actor
take the spotlight.
Alright, well, then maybe
you just couldn't handle
the idea of me directing you
in a large role.
I guess now we'll never know.
Everyone,
this first week of rehearsal
might be our hardest yet.
But I have faith
that if we work together,
we're gonna make
something really special.
Act One.
Toni, you're looking well!
Oh! Thank you.
And you must be Baya!
Uh, it's Bea, for Beatrice.
Apologies, of course.
My kid's a huge fan of
the police show you direct on.
- Oh.
- "The... Newbie"?
- Thank you, that's sweet.
- I myself don't watch TV.
Hm...
Uh, Juan,
before we get to our work today,
um... I have some personal news.
Watching this festival blossom
over the last 40 years
into an institution
has been the honour of my life.
But this season will be my last.
My dear Toni,
I speak on behalf of the board
when I say
it's been our absolute pleasure.
Your timing is impeccable.
The board was gonna wait
until the season was over
to present it to you,
but if you're planning
to retire anyway,
we received a buyout offer
for the festival.
What?
From... from who?
They prefer to remain anonymous,
but I can say
it's a media company
and a generous offer.
Is this the same company
that bought out
the Woodridge Festival
last spring?
I can neither confirm nor deny.
Do you know that they stream
every opening night online?
God, the audacity.
Downsized cast and crew,
the cut out shows.
We ended up hiring several
of the people they laid off.
Yeah, this festival,
it must stay independent.
I want that too,
but I am only one vote.
From the board's perspective,
if you leave
and we don't have a proper
successor for festival head...
We have a proper successor.
My Bea.
I wasn't aware
that was the plan.
This is the new plan.
I've been preparing for this
my entire life, Juan.
Literally.
Interesting.
As you know, even though
you founded the festival, Toni,
the board must unanimously
approve a new festival head.
You need to
prove yourself capable
these next few weeks, Bea.
Of course.
Yes.
And how, in your mind,
would I do that?
The board will want to see how
Taming of the Shrew
fares under your guidance.
Like with your celebrity friend,
for instance.
Well, Hannah Michaels is
an incredibly dedicated actress.
She's diving into this character
with her whole heart.
I... I can assure you, she's
way more than just a celebrity.
Well,
that will be important to see.
If it's a critical
and financial success,
then there's no reason
not to approve you to take over.
What in the world was that?
It's bigger than me.
It's bigger than us.
Mom, this is bad.
I called my agent this week
and I passed on directing
more episodes of "The Newbie"
because I didn't know
there were more hoops
to jump through.
Well, there won't be
once your Taming of the Shrew
is a smash hit.
Which I can't guarantee!
Oh, you've got this.
And you heard Juan.
I mean, if we don't nail
this final show of the season,
they're gonna sell the festival.
It's all got so much
pressure on it.
We don't have another choice.
Okay, welcome to our
second week of rehearsals.
I have decided to set this play
on a stock trading room floor.
I'm also exploring the idea
of blending modern
and Elizabethan costumes.
Stay with me; it's critical
that we keep these characters
relevant to a modern audience.
Good luck.
- Benny...?
- Mm-hm?
Something to share?
Ah, in my experience,
Shakespeare done classically
never steers you wrong.
Just gimme one...
quick second.
Can I talk to you, please?
Just because you can't imagine
relevant ways
of bringing Shakespeare
to the 21st century
doesn't mean I can't.
I respect tradition.
I was taught tradition too,
just not traditionally.
Learn the rules so you know
when to break them.
That's the entire message
of the play.
- No, it's not.
- Well, it is to me.
Am I the only one seeing
electricity between those two?
Oh, no.
We all see it.
You know what? They'd make
a great couple, if only...
If only they could agree on...
anything?
If Shakespeare were alive today,
he would almost certainly...
Love comes in many forms.
Grab a snack while
they go another round?
Yeah.
Okay.
- You want a revolution.
- You want dusty museum pieces!
"Those who forget the past
are doomed to repeat it."
Can we just start
the rehearsal, please?
That would be difficult.
Where did everyone go?
Oh, probably to the tavern
for a pint and a round of darts.
Maybe two, depending on how long
you two keep this nonsense up.
Time's ticking.
Can you please
get everybody back, Doug?
Thank you, Doug.
I appreciate you, Doug.
Okay.
Come on,
what's a little creative debate
between like-minded
artists, hmm?
No, no.
I don't have time for your...
your Gersten shenanigans.
There's things going on
that you don't know about.
I knew you were
keeping a secret.
Come on.
My mom's retiring...
and I wanna take over
as festival head.
Wow.
But the board
has a buyout offer on the table.
- They might sell the festival?
- They might.
If they don't approve me
to take over,
then the festival
as we know it is over.
This play has to be a success,
Benny.
I need your help,
for the festival's sake.
We can't let it happen.
- So, you'll help me?
- Of course I will.
Truce?
No, "truce" means
we'll fight again another day.
Alright,
so, what's the right word?
- Peace?
- Peace.
Okay, well,
now we just need to figure out
who's right about
how to make the show a success,
you or me.
Me.
Ah.
What could go wrong?
So, how was your
first week and a half?
Lovely.
You getting any sleep at all?
A little.
I was up way too late
texting last night.
Well, coffee, stat.
Got a long day
of rehearsal ahead of us.
By the way,
I hate to do this to you,
but you're gonna have to have
all of your lines
fully memorized by this weekend.
Oh, yeah,
I'm already halfway there.
That is, up to Act 2-ish.
Hmm...
Hannah's hilarious.
She's taking witty text banter
to a whole new level.
You two seem to have
really hit it off.
Yeah, she's just funny
and down-to-earth, you know?
I watched her show.
She's a very talented actress.
She's the whole package.
Whoa...
Easy there, Clay.
Save your feelings
for the stage, buddy.
She's just...
super cool, is all.
Sure, she's cool today,
tomorrow it's a crush,
in a week
you're head over heels,
and by opening night,
you're putting it all at risk.
Falling for your leading lady
is a rookie move.
Trust me, showmances don't work.
Are you talking about
you and Bea?
What?
No.
I'm talking generally,
as a guy who's been around
a long time.
Never works out.
Never.
Okay, can we talk
about something
other than Shakespeare
for a second?
Not my strong suit, but sure.
What's up with you and Benny?
There's some heavy-duty
flirting going on.
What?
Are you insane?!
We're not flirting!
We're... we're debating.
We're working through things.
Could have fooled me!
No, no, no, no.
That's the way
that Benny and I are.
It's... it's our process.
It's not romantic at all.
- So, you're friends, then?
- Well, I wouldn't say that.
- Enemies?
- Please.
Bitter rivals.
Hannah, it's...
complicated.
There is a history there.
We... were together.
- There it is!
- For a very short time!
Why'd you break up?
We just weren't a good match.
So, no hard feelings,
no hearts broken,
no lingering feelings
on either side at all?
Do you know what, it was
such a long time ago,
and... and we've moved on;
we've both had other
relationships, and...
now it's just like
we're on the same plane.
You know?
We just have a shorthand.
And it's not a romantic plane?
No. I-I find him
incredibly irritating.
Well, that's too bad.
I was hoping
we could double-date.
Double-date?
Who are you dating?
No, I dunno.
I mean theoretically.
So, how's it goin'
with Petruchio?
Oh, I am totally lost right now.
Kate and Petruchio's
relationship
doesn't make any sense.
They fight like crazy,
but in an affectionate
kinda way.
I know.
It's complex.
Ask your director.
Yeah, but you got insight.
Can't you help me out?
I'm just a fellow actor, Clay.
You know,
there's this rumour going around
that Toni might be retiring
as head of the festival.
Where'd you hear that?
It's a tight-knit group.
Word gets around.
I assume Bea's taking over?
She is.
Bea's brilliant.
You know, capable,
a very imaginative director.
- Mm-hm.
- And a leader.
Although she does have
some impossible shoes to fill.
Pretty brave to follow up
an icon like Toni Bishop,
especially when she's your mom.
Which I can fancy more
than any other.
Minion, thou liest!
Is't not...
Hortensio.
Oh!
Okay.
Hortensio, thou liest!
Is't not...
Bianca...
Sorry, you're Bianca.
- Yeah.
- Okay, let's take five.
Argh!
Yeah, yeah.
Maggie, thank you.
I'm so sorry, Bea.
It's just, there's so many names
and it's just so much dialogue,
and the scenes are just so long.
Do you remember
that scene that we shot
on the hospital rooftop?
Um, it was that
really long scene that you had
to memorize on the show?
- Yeah.
- How did you do that?
I don't know, I just
paced around until it stuck.
Oh, that's perfect.
Why don't you two
walk to the market
and you can run lines?
I know.
I'll go find Clay.
Oh no, Maggie's here.
Maggie, are you free?
Yeah, Maggie can do it.
Maggie's...
Oh, he's already
texting me back.
Oh.
Thank you, Bea.
I'll be back soon,
and I will know my lines.
Okay.
Perfect.
The food market's at, you know,
1 o'clock on a Wednesday.
Really good.
What's this one?
Aah!
Oh!
What are you doing here?
- Same as you.
- Come on.
I'm following the lovebirds.
They're not lovebirds!
They're running lines.
Then why are you following them?
I wanna make sure
they stay focused.
Hannah learns her lines best
when she's walking.
Can you give me some space,
please?
Maybe she's struggling with
Shakespeare's wording.
It might help her if she
shortens the lines down
to the first letter
in each word.
And uses the acronym
to trigger her memory.
Of course!
I forgot about that old trick.
Good idea.
Does it hurt your brain when
you're forced to compliment me?
Luckily, it rarely happens.
- Oh! They're heading this way!
- Gah!
Benny...?
Shh!
It's the energy
from the audience
that makes it so great,
don't you think?
Be honest...
- What are they doing?
- I can't see.
You'll be fine.
I have two weeks!
That's it.
That's tons of time.
I don't know if I can do this.
I'll be here to help.
Thank you.
Like I said...
lovebirds.
Oh, no...
this is not good for my play!
No, it's not.
Okay, well, why are we hiding?
Why don't we go confront them?
No, you can't just
ambush them out in public.
I'll talk to Clay,
you talk to Hannah.
And say what?
Remind them that showmances
are a terrible idea.
And they can completely
distract you from your work.
And they always end
in a miserable break up.
That doesn't always
have to happen.
Oh, no?
Can we stay focused
on the play, please?
Yeah, yeah.
Um, yeah, fine by me.
- Thank you.
- No, no, no...
Thank you.
Whoa, Maggie!
You look stunning in that dress.
It's gorgeous, right?
Where's Hannah?
She's supposed to be
in fittings all morning.
I'm here!
And I brought coffee.
You're late.
I know, I had to jump
on a call with my agents.
Since we announced
that I'm doing Shakespeare,
some pretty cool projects
are coming my way
that you'd be perfect to direct.
Thank you. Not that that's
an excuse for being late.
I'm sorry.
That's really exciting.
Thank you for thinking of me.
You got it, sister.
Hannah, I actually... I need
to talk to you about something.
Ladies, will you
just give us a moment?
Maggie,
I'm gonna need that dress back.
- I was thinking I could keep it.
- No.
- Okay. No, no.
- Okay.
Oh, no.
Am I in trouble?
It is about the play.
You and Clay.
We thought
we were hiding it well.
You thought kissing
in the middle of the market
was hiding it well?
I can't help it!
He's the nicest guy
I've ever met.
He's so sweet,
and there's just this...
electricity between us.
I'm disappointing you.
No...
You can date whoever you want.
It's not just dating.
We're falling in love, Bea.
You've only known each other
a couple of weeks!
Plus, you're playing characters
that are falling in love.
That's not real love, Hannah.
That... that's called
festival love.
No, it's not festival love, Bea.
It's... love love.
Okay, sit down.
Come on.
I've been in your shoes before.
When Benny and I were doing
Romeo and Juliet, it was like...
we were meant to be.
I still don't understand what
happened between the two of you.
It was a bad review.
It killed me.
"Bea Bishop is distracted
"and uninspired
in the role of Juliet."
I'm sorry,
you have a bad review
from 20 years ago memorized?
Well, I'm paraphrasing,
but the gist was I stunk.
I doubt that.
Why did that mean
you and Benny had to break up?
Well, after the review came out,
I decided
I never wanted to act again.
Benny was this shooting star.
I mean,
everyone knew he was gonna
do incredible things
on the stage,
just like my mother, who had
an amazing acting career,
and then
she founded the festival,
and I was just never
gonna measure up.
What did Benny say?
I never talked to him about it.
I bumbled my way through
the rest of the run,
I broke it off with him,
and I started
studying directing.
So, you still
haven't discussed it?
I-I don't wanna revisit that.
Scaredy-cat!
Hey! I didn't even wanna
talk to you about it,
except that I need you
to understand why I'm worried.
Hannah, if you go out
on that stage
and all you're thinking about
is how much you love Clay,
the audience isn't gonna
see Kate's story.
They're gonna see Hannah,
the TV actress who's...
got a crush on her co-star.
And I won't let that
kind of review happen to you.
I won't.
I get it.
- You do?
- Yeah.
You're gonna be
so good in this play.
And this dress is amazing!
Well, you believing in me
is all I need.
Thanks, Bea.
Aah!
Good work, good job.
Alright, now we'll show you
a little bit of a death scene.
Hi-yah...!
- Hi-yah!
- Aahhh!
Alright. Good job, guys.
Great job, great job.
- Good job.
- Thanks, everyone.
Good job, everybody.
Now, that was fun.
Rehearsal, on the other hand,
different story.
You still struggling
with your character?
Yeah.
You know, I asked Bea about it,
and she guided me through
in a really smart way, but...
I still don't get why Petruchio
can't be honest
about his feelings towards Kate.
Well, there's no guarantee that
she feels the same way, right?
It's risky.
Isn't all love risk, though?
Maybe Petruchio's
been hurt in the past.
Maybe he's had a broken heart.
Or maybe he's just an idiot
and he needs
to get over himself.
If he would just
be honest with her,
maybe he wouldn't have to be
miserable all the time.
Are we still
talking about Petruchio?
Petruchio is... messy.
Says the wrong thing,
makes bad choices.
But like every good character,
he'll figure himself out
in the end.
Nail down where he is in
each scene along that journey,
and you'll have it.
I promise.
- You make it so simple.
- Mm-hm.
You're overthinking it.
Thanks, man.
Yeah.
It's just
a little friendly advice.
And speaking of advice...
you and Hannah are a thing, huh?
Don't bother trying to deny it.
When you spend all day
in rehearsal
convincing your mind that
you're in love with someone,
it's natural that
you fall for them.
But it's festival love.
I don't know.
I've never felt
this way about...
anyone before.
Steel yourself, Sir Clay!
The last thing you want
is a broken heart, buddy.
Alright?
Yeah.
Good work.
Oof!
You're gonna have
to do better than that!
I haven't played
this in forever.
Oh, no, you were supposed
to be our secret ringer.
You've really become a big
part of this event, haven't you?
I think it's important
to give back to the community
that supports us.
I think you've gotten
really good at getting people
excited about theatre.
Hmph.
Blam!
See that?
That's how you do it.
- Sorry, I blinked.
- Oh.
Have you ever thought about
becoming a teacher, Benny?
Back in the day.
Luckily for me,
the acting thing worked out.
Those who can't do, teach.
Am I right?
No, those who have
put in years of hard work
and earned the respect
of their peers...
they teach.
Passing knowledge on to a future
generation is a privilege.
What are you doing?
You've completely
locked out your elbows.
- No, I haven't.
- Okay, just...
just, um... just loosen
your stance a little bit.
Loosen your stance.
Loosen your hips.
- Okay.
- Okay? Just...
Sorry.
Okay.
There you go, okay.
Just...
take it easy, okay?
Okay.
Try again.
Yikes!
I knew that wasn't gonna work.
Hey, how did it go with Clay?
Ah, we're good. He gets it.
Hannah?
Yeah, she gets it.
By the way, I think
you should teach everybody
that memorization method...
the acronym one.
Nah, you should teach 'em.
No, you teach them.
Everybody looks up to you.
- They do?
- Yeah, of course.
I can't give
fellow actors a note.
You're the director.
Ah, sometimes actors connect
with each other differently.
Well, you were an actor
once upon a time.
A distracted and uninspired one.
What are you talking about?
The review...?
From Romeo and Juliet?
Ah, reviews are just noise.
Well, that review took me down.
Made me quit acting.
You don't remember that?
I remember you leaving.
Is it time...
for the great rematch?
I can see that you're ready.
Alright, get into position.
Oh...!
This is gonna be
one for the ages.
Come on, Bea.
Is everybody warmed up?
Should we stretch?
Alright, you're up first.
So, the masquerade party is a...
tradition to celebrate
opening night?
A few days
before the final show opens,
we have this
amazing costume party.
It's the best.
My mask looks... unwell.
Well, I think I'm kind of
nailing it over here.
Yeah, you are.
Can I try it on?
No, it's not dry.
We're done.
I know, I was just
paying you a compliment.
I don't need
compliments right now.
What's up with you two?
You got this real...
Bea and Benny thing
going on right now.
What? No.
No, we do not.
Hannah thinks Bea and Benny
are star-crossed lovers.
Hannah, you're new here,
so let me explain something.
The only thing
that Bea and Benny do
when they're together is fight.
I promise you, what's happening
with Bea and Benny is love.
Weird, witty, passionate love.
I mean, look at them.
That's nothing but love.
Even if Bea and Benny's
non-traditional chemistry
is obvious to us,
they'll never see it.
They're too stubborn.
They need a little...
push.
We need to get them
out of their own way.
How?
The only way Bea
will feel safe enough
to allow her feelings
for Benny...
would be to prove...
that Benny is head over heels
in love with her.
But Benny would also need
that same proof
in order to even admit
his feelings for her.
Exactly.
So... they may need
a little help
from their friends?
Uh-huh.
Now this is getting really good.
Right?
Yeah.
Incoming!
Bea. Incoming.
I love female directors.
He's obsessed with her.
The only thing
that he focuses on is Bea.
Going on and on about
her... her confidence
and... and fearlessness.
Have you heard him swoon
about her... hair?
Her...
gorgeous, speckled brunette...
Uh, not to mention her...
perfect posture.
Yeah!
If you're in love
with someone, just tell them.
Benny's terrified of
what we're all terrified of...
unrequited love.
He's got a notebook filled
with poems about her.
He swore me to secrecy.
If she rejected him,
I think that'd break him
in half.
Oh!
Me!
Hello, boys!
Oh...
Hey, Bea.
Hi!
- What do you think?
- I'm confused.
The costumes are confusing?
Oh.
No, it... it's a...
work in progress.
So, should we go back
to rehearsal, then?
Yes.
Good.
I'll get... I just need
one minute to myself.
Will you just tell Doug Berrie
I'm on my way?
But don't stress him out.
Tell him I'm like one minute.
60 seconds.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, sure thing.
- Good.
- Great. Thank you.
Awesome.
- See ya out there, boss.
- Okay, boss!
Whoa...
Why are our bodies...
weak... and smooth?
Soft and weak.
Ah, I promised Bea I would
have my lines memorized by now!
Where is he?
Doug Berrie said this is Benny's
usual treadmill time.
- Oh!
- Benny, hey.
Act natural.
The... the...
a sauna is the...
is the key to brain health.
Yeah, I saw a video about that.
Yeah, actually.
Benny's listening to music,
right? He can't hear us?
No, he's got his headphones in.
You can keep going.
As I was saying...
it's sad that he has no idea
about her true feelings for him.
You really think
he doesn't know?
I mean, if I were him,
I would've figured it out
a long time ago.
But... pfft!
You know Benny.
So... what did she say?
Benny?
- Benny!
Benny...
Okay.
He's not listening.
There's never been
anyone like him.
And not only is he brilliant...
but also hot.
Mm-hm.
Oh, and that he's
in incredible shape.
I believe the phrase
she used was,
"Looks great in a T-shirt."
Uh... uh, so,
why doesn't she just tell him?
Well, she's been writing
and rewriting this letter to him
for the past year,
confessing her true feelings.
But every time she finishes
a version, she just deletes it.
That's crazy.
It's like,
just kiss him already!
Well, what are you gonna do?
We just gotta let Bea be Bea.
Um, I gotta shower
before rehearsal,
so, uh, let's get outta here.
Bye, Benny.
Can I get a sleeve, too, for it?
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Fancy meeting you here.
Yeah.
Love coffee.
Were you, uh...
hoping to find me here?
What? Me? No, no.
I-I need fuel for rehearsal.
Yes, yes.
Mainline that caffeine!
- Ooh, boy!
- Boo-oy!
- Should we head over?
- Yup.
I just need
to ask you something.
Something?
What something is that?
It's about the play.
- The play?
- Yeah.
You wanted to check in
with me about the play?
Yeah.
I think the thing
I'm struggling with
is that everything
these two characters do
doesn't line up with them
loving each other.
That's what the story is.
But is that really
the best version?
Because, to me,
if they were on the same side,
it'd be a way better story.
- You mean if they were a team?
- Yes.
I'm talking about
Kate and Petruchio.
- Right.
- Yeah.
How would that work?
Well, you'll hate this...
because it's an untraditional
take on a traditional play.
Oh, you wanna set it
on the moon now?
It's a little late
in the rehearsal process
- to fit the cast in spacesuits.
- Stop.
What if, instead of Kate being
forced to marry Petruchio...
she's just in it for the dowry?
Say more.
She's convinced her father
that she's being compliant,
- but that's her strategy.
- Why would she do that?
Because she and Petruchio
are scheming together.
And then that's how
they fall in love,
and then they get the money,
and then they outwit everybody.
Does the text
support it, though?
In spots, yes.
Unless you split
the dialogue up between them.
- Double up some lines.
- Exactly.
Have them said by both of them.
That way, it's all still
Mr. Shakespeare's words, but...
You're just using
them differently.
Purists will be mad.
Heck, you'll be mad.
You'll be madder than anyone.
Oh, you know every
alarm bell in my body
is clanging like crazy.
But I also know if anyone
can pull it off, it's you.
You really mean that?
You know I do.
What about the board?
If it doesn't work, they won't
approve me as festival head.
They will,
if the audience loves it.
And this is a solid way
to do that.
I can't believe I was gonna
make the whole play
about battling stockbrokers.
I know.
I nearly passed out.
It's what you said about
historical context, right?
So, we'll do, in addition
to the hybrid costumes,
we'll have them
share dialogue as well.
And if you adjust the lines
just a bit,
this can become a love story
that everyone relates to.
I can't believe you just
said those words out loud.
Me neither.
Are we having
a creative conversation?
We are.
Without fighting?
Yes, ma'am.
For the first time ever?
There is something
I wanna ask you.
There's something
I wanna ask you too.
Are we rehearsing
this thing or what?
We are burning daylight.
Time's a-tickin',
my pretty chickens.
Yes, Doug,
we're right behind you.
Après thee.
Right in front of you.
- Is everyone else...?
- Yeah.
- One, two, three!
- Shakespeare!
Ha-ha!
We got this.
- We do.
- I love this.
Okay.
I care not.
Nay, hear you, Kate:
in sooth, you 'scape not so.
I'm so sorry, just,
can we go one more time?
- You ready?
- Yeah.
I care not.
Nay, hear you, Kate:
in sooth, you 'scape not so.
Um...
Uh... uh!
I chafe you if I tarry.
Let me go.
No, not a whit.
- What are you doing?
- Low blood sugar, I guess.
I'm trying to concentrate.
Because we open
in less than a week,
and you're having a snack.
I'm just deep in the character.
Right, you're
the seasoned theatre actor
and I'm just a TV person who
doesn't know what she's doing?
Okay.
Let's take a breath. Um...
This is not easy, right?
So, let's take it from...
Hannah?
I'll go after her...
so you can keep
going with everyone else.
Thank you, Benny.
Really?
Hey, there.
Hannah?
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Totally okay.
Have you ever felt...
truly terrible at your job?
Sure.
Years ago, Toni,
she got some funding
to train a handful of actors.
I applied, I got in,
and I moved here to study.
I was the only actor
who came from out of town.
It was terrifying.
And back then,
I think I truly was terrible,
as you phrased it.
How did you get over that?
Bea was in that workshop too.
We were kids.
The first day, we were
put together in a scene
as Rosencrantz and Guildenstern.
Not the most romantic
of pairings.
No.
Not at all.
But we crushed it.
After that, I stopped
worrying about if I was good.
I just wanted
to show up for her.
She was fearless.
Patient.
She had
this playfulness about her.
It freed me.
It's still there.
I wanna crush it
like that with Clay.
Good, 'cause there's still time.
Thank you
for talking to me, Benny.
Mm-hm.
Now I just need to figure out
how to get these blasted lines
into my brain.
I don't think the acronym trick
is working for me.
I have another method that
might help with memorization.
It's pretty easy
once you learn it.
Okay.
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, let me teach it to you.
Have you heard of
a memory palace?
Yup.
It's not nearly as complicated
as that, don't worry.
- Try that, but...
- It's making her work for it.
- Right!
- Basically.
Right, make him earn it.
Just play with it.
Mom! Juan! Ah!
What brings you by?
We were just going over
some financials for next season.
Is Hannah Michaels
not rehearsing today?
Oh, she's just getting some air.
Awfully confident of her
to skip rehearsal.
And where's Clay?
He's getting some...
other air.
Really?
And in the meantime
we're sorting out
some of the blocking
with Don and Maggie.
Have you met Maggie?
Juan, come here!
Maggie!
You two will love each other.
Yeah, ask her about Ashland.
Is anything wrong?
My two leads aren't
speaking to each other,
and if I don't
pull off this play
to critical
and financial success,
then I won't get my dream job
and then the whole thing
gets sold off for parts
and then I leave your legacy
in tatters.
But other than that,
no, nothing's wrong.
That was dramatic.
Where's Benny?
He usually brings out
the best in you.
You know, he actually might be
the reason I'm spiralling.
Ooh.
Let me guess.
You've realized
that there's still
something special between you?
How am I the very
last person to know about this?
Oh, I hope they didn't
give you any spoilers.
It's a 400-year-old play;
I already know the ending.
Oh, yes, but you don't know
what surprises Bea has in store.
True.
True, the board and I
will have a keen eye
on the audience's reaction
opening night,
and box office receipts,
of course.
Of course.
Yes.
And just wait until you see
how perfect it's all gonna be.
I myself am dying to see.
I'm just dying.
Am I... interrupting?
Looks like you and the bard are
having an intense discussion.
He's got a lot to say about
my impostor syndrome.
"Who do you think you are, Bea?
"This play is gonna be
a disaster, Bea."
At least Shakespeare knows
how to pronounce your name
correctly.
Where's your witty comeback?
Mm, trying a new move.
Looks like you have to sneeze.
What?
I never apologized for how
I ended things between us.
It wasn't right.
Bea, it's fine.
It's very obviously not fine
if you're still upset about it.
I shouldn't have said anything.
I'm sorry.
Stop apologizing!
I'm the one apologizing here.
This is my apology time.
By all means, then.
I'm sorry.
Accepted.
Is that it?
Why didn't you wanna play
Petruchio with me directing?
I don't wanna answer
that question right now.
Why not?
Because we have bigger problems.
You think it's possible
that our plan to break up
Hannah and Clay might have...
Made things worse
for the play and not better?
- Do you think?
- Yeah, maybe a little.
Oh, no.
I fear had we not meddled,
those two crazy kids
might have actually
stood a chance.
We have to fix this.
The play opens
in less than a week.
How do we do that?
We approach them together
and we talk to them.
As a united front.
You think the two of us
should advise them on love?
Maybe we leave it alone.
Yeah, you know, chances are
it's gonna sort itself out.
They're both adults.
Yeah.
And then worst case,
we'll just trick them
into falling back in love.
Oh... that does sound
a whole lot more fun.
- So, you're in?
- Of course I'm in.
The masquerade awaits.
And you, sir, are not invited.
Ooh! Burn.
We're gonna have
a lot of work to do
to get those two back together.
You clean up nice.
I guess.
Thanks.
You look alright, too.
I guess.
Thanks.
- Shall we?
- We shall.
Party... time.
This is fun.
I can't believe
I agreed to this.
I can't either.
Something's come over you.
Maybe something
has come over me.
Like...
this.
Yes.
Game face is on.
Regroup in ten.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Tankard of mead for yourself?
Thanks.
You're not having fun, are you?
No, I am.
I'm just trying
to stay undistracted.
The last thing I want
is to disappoint you, Bea.
Or let the festival down.
Ah, but you forget,
I believe in you.
And before I opened my mouth,
you were doing
a really good job.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, I think I can do it now.
Benny really helped me out.
- He did?
- He's amazing.
He is amazing.
Ha!
I knew you liked him.
Drink your mead, lady.
Oof...
That was quite the blow-up
at rehearsal today.
I guess you were right.
Festival love.
I... could be wrong.
And it's the real thing.
I'm sorry, what?
I know, buddy,
it seems crazy I can be wrong.
Alas... there is always
that possibility.
You know who else is amazing?
Clay.
I say go for it.
Let yourself fall in love with
a genuinely good guy who,
let's face it,
is perfect for you.
Life is short, and love is rare.
I don't know.
It's too late now.
Ah.
Go for phase two?
I really have to dance?
The time for subtlety
has passed.
Good luck, soldier.
May I have this dance?
Absolutely.
I don't feel like
dancing right now.
This is a party,
and you're gonna dance
whether you like it or not.
- You sound like my mom.
- Your mom sounds awesome.
Hi.
Can you just dance with me
so I can at least apologize?
I'm the one
who should be apologizing.
I can't believe that worked.
I think we should just
let nature take its course
from now on.
Listen, as long
as the play is back on track,
it is fine with me.
Oh, as if you can put
Bea Bishop, director,
on pause
for the rest of the night.
Yes, I'm wearing a mask!
I can be anyone I want.
Huh.
Hello.
My name is Sandy.
I like long walks on the beach
and men with trucks.
- Hm.
- What's your name?
I'm Dennis.
I drive a truck.
My hand is ready.
May it do him ease.
Now kiss me, Kate.
No.
You kiss me, sir.
Yes, that was it!
- Bravo!
- Incredible work.
And I know everybody's very
tired from last night's party,
so thank you so much
for hanging in there with me.
Um, Hannah,
you have got these lines down.
Yeah!
Now it's just about relaxing
into them, making them your own.
We share this tomorrow
with an audience.
Thank you so much, everybody.
Get some rest.
Hey...
How was that?
You can be honest.
Tell me.
Final dress rehearsal
is always tough.
You'll have to trust the magic
of this intimate venue
a little bit.
There's still some time.
Never enough time.
You gotta be gentle
with yourself, Bea.
You know what
you need right now?
A burger and a beer.
Ooh, that sounds really good.
Thanks.
How about we go for a bite?
A what?
Oh, uh, a bite.
Oh!
I thought you said "a date."
I was like...
No, I...
I said "bite."
Oh...
But yeah, a date.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's working.
Look at them.
Ah, 20 bucks says
they'll be fighting
the next time we see them.
I'd hate to think
what would happen
if they figured out
we tricked them.
No, they'll be
so head-over-heels in love
they won't care, trust me.
Well, you haven't been
wrong yet, so...
Is that what you're wearing?
If you want me to.
Well, hopefully
Bea can stay focused
and we'll all be employed
next year.
Wait,
what are you talking about?
The buyout offer.
If Bea isn't approved
to take over from Toni,
the board's gonna
sell the festival.
And what's the board
basing Bea's approval on?
Well, if I were a betting man,
I'd say on how well we pull off
Taming of the Shrew.
We have to nail it.
Yeah, and if we don't succeed,
this might be our last
Summer Shakespeare Festival.
No pressure, though, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, let's do that.
Huzzah!
My name is Joy Tidings.
Hi, Joy.
Here's your wee pint for you,
Benny.
You know,
when stress levels are high,
you don't need to do
the whole shtick.
Oh, thanks, Bea.
We'll have two Bard Burgers,
medium rare,
and a Macbeth Scotch Egg.
One of those for me, please.
- Thank you.
I think this is
our first burger together
since the night before
Romeo and Juliet opened.
Oh, you mean the night before
I decided to stop acting.
The tragedy of Bea Bishop.
You were a great actor.
You still are.
Well, the whole reason
I became an actor
in the first place was Toni.
I admire her so much.
But admiring
doesn't mean copying.
You know,
that's why I went to New York.
I always thought you left
because all we had
was festival love
and nothing more for you.
That's not what it was for me.
It broke my heart.
I wish I could go back in time
and I could
explain myself better.
Well, it feels like we're
going back in time right now.
- Mmm.
- Thanks.
Well, now we know.
No going back.
Only forward.
Cheers to that.
And to the new,
brilliant head of the festival.
All I can hear
is Hassan
whispering under his breath...
"I'm so sorry, baby."
Wait, didn't he marry the
director of that show, Peggy?
That lady's a legend.
They're still married!
No!
So amazing.
It's so good to see you laugh.
Oh.
Yeah, I almost forgot
tomorrow's opening night
and my two leads aren't ready,
and if they don't
knock it out of the park,
then I might not be
approved as festival head,
and then, who knows, there
might not even be a festival.
Oh, pfft.
You're Bea Bishop.
You can handle anything
that comes your way.
Hmm...
Okay, let me remind you
of the story of you.
You were unhappy acting, so you
became this amazing director.
Not only plays, but TV too.
And now you're gonna come in
and you're gonna revolutionize
this whole festival.
It's just pivot after pivot.
Reinvention.
Evolution.
Transformation.
To me, that much change
is terrifying,
but you make it look effortless.
You're an actor, Benny.
You change all the time
for a living.
That's different.
That's being other people
in other situations.
Sometimes...
you know, being myself, it's...
feels like it's...
impossible.
Well, I happen to like
who you are.
And your fellow actors do, too.
They respect you.
You could take over
the actors' workshop!
Why are you groaning?
Why... why is this a bad idea?
What are you doing?
- Ah, one second.
- What's happening?
- Okay.
Was winged Cupid blind?
Let's get outta here.
- The glasses.
- Oh, why?
I'm taking this.
As evidence?
For posterity.
They usually wait until Act Two.
I think they'd wait
until Act Seven or Eight
if plays had that many acts.
Right.
But, in real life,
kisses can happen at any time.
When you least expect it.
Like... right now.
Or, like, right now.
I'm so happy you told
the girls how you feel.
Wait, what girls?
Because I agree.
We've been drawn to each other
and we push each other
in a great way.
I didn't tell
the girls anything.
Apparently it was a...
a love... email?
I'm flattered that you noticed
I've been working out.
You know, I do feel
stronger, too.
Wait, someone told you
I have feelings for you?
I believe the words were...
"Looks good in a T-shirt".
But yes.
Who told you that, Benny?
Ah, I can't reveal my sources.
Well, you're the one
who's secretly writing
love poems, buddy.
By the way, my hair's
not speckled with anything.
I'm not... really into poetry.
And "speckled"?
What?
That's not the word I would use.
What word would you use?
I wouldn't use any word.
I...
Look, I'm just glad that you
talked to Hannah about me
because now we've been able to
get everything out in the open.
You heard I had feelings
for you from Hannah?
Uh...
it was more of
an overhear, but yes.
I overheard Clay and Don say
that you're obsessed with me.
I'm ob...?
Okay.
What am I missing here?
They set us up!
Wait, they meddled...
with our relationship?
Why would they do that?
Maybe because
we meddled with theirs,
so then they meddled right back?
Oh, those young, pretty,
meddling tricksters.
We almost kissed for no reason.
Wait...
No reason?
So, all of this between us,
this was just...
A trick?
- One second.
- Don't answer that.
We should probably
talk this through.
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
Hannah quit the play.
Hannah!
No, don't try
and change my mind.
My car is almost here.
Why are you doing this?
I didn't know the entire
festival is riding on this play.
Alright, let's sit down,
let's talk about this.
Whatever's bothering you,
we can figure it out.
Don't you hear me?
I'm leaving.
Okay,
I'm going to an airport hotel
and I'm booked on a flight out
tomorrow night.
I am not talented enough
to save this festival.
It'll be better for you
and the play
if you let Maggie take over.
Everybody's coming to see you.
The entire run of the show
is sold out.
No, it's...
it's too much pressure.
I promise
I will make it up to you, Bea.
How?
I got offered a role
in a limited series.
It's about a luxury resort
during World War II
in Portofino.
Whoa, that sounds really good.
It is.
I told my agents to
put you up for directing on it.
But I'm supposed to be
taking over the festival.
But is that
what you really want?
Because if not...
get on a plane,
come to the Italian coast.
Hey, I've been where you are,
and feeling like the only thing
you can do is run away,
but listen to me.
Whatever you're
running away from,
it's gonna catch up to you.
- I have to go. I'm sorry.
- Hannah...
Thank you.
Hannah...
I'm sorry it's so late,
everyone.
Okay,
what is with all the SOS texts?
Hannah quit.
She left.
Okay, it's gonna be fine.
I'll call and text her,
try to change her mind, Bea.
On the off chance that
that doesn't work,
we need to come up
with a backup plan.
Tomorrow night, we'll tell
everyone that Hannah is ill
and the part of Kate
will be played by Maggie.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, I can't.
You're the understudy.
Understudies are never ready
this early on in any play's run.
You know that.
Could we postpone the opening?
The entire future
of the festival's at risk.
There's only one logical option
at this point, Bea.
- What?
- You're playing Kate.
I'm what?
Vail your stomachs,
for it is no boot
to place your hand
below your husband's foot,
in token in...
of which duty...
No, we changed that.
What?
I don't... I...
Why did I think I could do this?
- Because you can.
- History is repeating itself.
No, it's not.
This is gonna work.
You have the lines, but you're
thinking like Bea the director.
If you're gonna be Kate,
you have to think like Kate.
Be here.
Alright, with your Petruchio.
Partner's foot.
And place your hands
below your partner's foot.
In token of which duty,
if she please.
My hand is ready,
may it do her ease.
Come on.
Kiss me, Kate.
You would have made
a brilliant Petruchio.
Please tell me this is working.
It was, Doug.
Yeah,
let's take it from the top.
- Tick-tock.
- Yeah, it's good.
Yeah, thank you, Doug.
Thank you.
Good job.
- Okay.
- Good.
To make a stale of me among...
No!
To make a stale of me
amongst these mates.
Ugh, I cannot believe
I'm still learning these lines
the day of the show!
I've been texting her all day.
I even left a voice memo
of me reciting a sonnet.
She ghosted me.
You know this has
nothing to do with you, right?
This is about Hannah
and her confidence.
She's afraid.
Yeah, I guess just keep trying.
Wow.
By the way, I haven't had
a chance to say this, but...
I think you'd make
a great festival head.
Regardless of what Benny says.
What did Benny say?
Oh, that you had
impossible shoes to fill.
How's everybody feeling, huh?
Will you go and run
Act Four with Clay
while I figure out
what to do with my hair?
- Of course.
- This is a nightmare.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
You got this.
No, I definitely
do not got this.
You look amazing,
so you're already halfway there.
No, that's not
what this is about.
I don't belong on that stage.
I belong backstage
in jeans and a baseball cap.
I learned that years ago.
That's what Romeo and Juliet
taught me.
You're gonna be
head of the festival next.
Am I?
Or do I have
"impossible shoes to fill"?
What?
You said that to Clay.
That was just
a figure of speech.
Hm?
Toni's set a high standard.
So, that is how you really feel.
You know, you believing in me
made me believe in myself,
which made me feel like
I deserved this job
because I'd be actually
good at it.
And now I feel like I should
just follow Hannah to Italy.
- Italy?
- Yeah.
'Cause at least there
I'd be doing a job
I know I'm actually good at.
Where would that leave us?
That leaves us as two people
who fell for a trick, Benny.
I guess it does.
Silly us.
Okay, everybody,
this is your three-hour warning.
We only have three hours
till showtime.
Say that she rail;
why, then I'll tell her plain...
she sings as sweetly
as a nightingale.
Okay.
Let's do this.
You good?
Yeah.
I think...
Look, I just wanted to say,
you really helped me
with this part, Benny.
You're welcome.
It's really cool
to have a mentor.
It's cool to be one.
I still can't believe we're
doing this without Hannah.
If the lines get messy,
just play it off like
Kate and Petruchio
are on the same
secret wavelength at all times.
Like you and Bea?
Once this is all over,
remind me how mad I am
at all of you,
making Bea and me believe that
we were in love with each other.
Was it really a trick
if it's true?
How many hours until places?
Uh, less than two at this point.
Hi, how are you?
Juan and the whole board
are here.
The entire run of the show
is officially sold out
and it's only opening night!
Okay, everybody,
this is your places call
for the top of the show.
Wait, has anybody
laid eyes on Benny?
Uh, I haven't actually
seen him in a while.
What?!
First Hannah, now Benny?
This can't be happening!
I'm here!
- Hannah!
- Bea, I'm here.
What changed your mind?
I was going through airport
security and all of a sudden
I hear this voice yell,
"Don't get on the plane.
"We need you."
It was like I was in a rom-com.
It wasn't me.
It was Benny.
Benny?
Did you run through the airport
in your costume?
Yep.
Hannah, can you go on?
Of course.
Alright,
let's get you in this dress!
Doug Berrie,
I need you to stall.
The play has started.
Yes, except that Kate
doesn't go on until
after Lucentio's monologue.
And Lucentio is in a very
slow-talking mode right, Don?
Got it, Bea.
Alright, come on, let's go.
Come on!
Okay...
Alright!
And practice rhetoric
in your common talk...
I've thought about
what you said.
About not running away.
Everyone here has worked
so hard, and I realized...
I just want to make you proud.
I couldn't possibly be
more proud of you.
And I'm so sorry
if I made you feel
distracted or unfocused or...
Well, I was distracted.
And unfocused.
But I think that's where
I'm at my best.
And I think that's where
Kate is at her best, too.
What do you mean?
Dealing with her
parents' legacy...
a life that's short
where love is rare.
It's just one big juggling act.
No one's ever gonna be
perfect at it, right?
Go kill it out there.
I always do.
Thou must be married
to no man but me.
For I am he
am born to tame you, Kate.
And I am she
am born to tame you, sir.
And I'll go from
a wild Kate to a Kate
conformable as other
household Kates...
Hannah's doing beautifully.
The audience is eating
out of the palm of her hand.
I knew she had it in her.
I can't believe
you brought her back.
Why'd you do that?
Why do you think?
I'd do anything to help you,
Bea.
You belong here.
And you deserve to be here.
As the head of the festival.
This is what you want, isn't it?
Unless I'm wrong.
Maybe what you really want
is in Italy.
You missed your cue!
See how they kiss and court!
Signor Lucentio,
here is my hand.
Hey.
There you are.
What are you doing out here?
Oh...
Don't you wanna see the ending?
Has the ending changed?
Well, you never know.
People can surprise you.
Oh, that's true.
Mom, do you remember the review
that I got for Romeo and Juliet?
The one that called you
"distracted and uninspired"?
That's the one.
Mom, that review
is the reason...
that I decided to stop acting.
Because how could I possibly
live up to the great
Toni Bishop?
Oh...
Mm-hm...
Honey...
You know, your success here
is not about what you're doing.
It's all about who you are.
And you are the leader
of this festival.
Thank you, Mom.
You wanna tell me
what's really going on?
Benny.
Ah-hah.
Bea...
You were always
my first priority.
But after you...
I was married to my job.
Mm.
This festival was my great love.
But...
if I have any regret,
it's that I didn't
take care of my heart.
Hm.
Take care of your heart, honey.
He drives me nuts.
You drive him nuts.
It's nothing but love.
Sometimes you have to realize
that the only thing
standing in your way...
is you.
Oh, the play's ending soon.
Hey, Mom, why don't you
come out on that stage with me?
Let's give them
one more bow here tonight.
No, this is your moment, baby.
You go enjoy it.
For it is no boot,
to place your hand
below your partner's foot,
in token of which duty,
if she please.
My hand is ready,
may it do him ease.
Come on and kiss me, Kate.
No, you kiss me, sir.
Thank you!
Hi!
Congratulations.
Great job.
Mm, thank you!
You're welcome.
You were great, by the way.
Hi.
An absolutely wonderful
opening night, Bea.
You're right, I admit I was
skeptical about Hannah Michaels,
but she really delivered.
Everyone did.
But especially you.
Thank you so much.
The subtle changes were clever.
You made this look easy,
which is no surprise.
Yeah, no, not a surprise to me.
The entire audience
was enthralled.
And the board?
We all agree the future
of the festival is safe
in your capable hands, Bea.
Thank you, Juan.
I couldn't agree more.
I won't let you down, sir.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Hi!
I've been looking for you.
You were?
What for?
What did you say to Hannah
to get her to come back?
Oh, you mean after
I caught my breath?
Yeah.
I told her how we were both
so lucky to know you.
And that she didn't
need to worry about failing.
All she had to do was remember
that Bea Bishop believes in her.
She doesn't need anything else.
You make people wanna be brave.
And if I was,
I'd admit that I love mentoring.
But that doesn't mean
that I can't act as well.
If you believe in me...
I think I can do anything.
I have another question.
Of course you do.
Why didn't you wanna play
Petruchio with me directing?
Because it's true.
I've never gotten over you, Bea.
All these years...
I still loved you.
And I thought
working that closely,
it would be impossible
to hide my feelings for you.
As it turns out...
I was right.
I'm glad you were right.
- Any more questions?
- No.
But I have answers.
I'm not gonna go to Italy.
I'm gonna stay right here...
and I'm gonna run this festival.
New moves.
Smart.
And I want to be with you.
I'm with you, honey.
Even when I give you
a hard time?
Especially then.
New moves, indeed.
But you know I'm gonna
need help running this place.
And I think you and I
are a lot stronger together.
Well...
I could consider it.
I mean, as long as you
run things strictly according
to classical tradition.
Oh, kiss me, you fool.